翻译、时间轴、压制：up主
What makes a good dog fight?
什么是狗斗的取胜因素呢
The skill of the pilot
飞行员的技巧
or the performance of the plane.
还是大股东的飞机
The suspense miles.
在互相纠缠的那段距离里
Your faith on the line.
弹道上的信仰
No second chances.
没有第二次机会
Heartbeat increases.
加速的心跳
Every muscle in motion.
每处肌肉的颤栗
You can hear the engines roar.
你能听见引擎的轰鸣声
The propeller spin.
螺旋桨的冲击着空气
The planes vibrates as they push them to the very edge.
飞机抖动着 犹如达到了极限状态
Time slows down
时间缓慢地流逝着
and for a brief moment they are invincible
仿佛有一瞬间这一切都消失了
alone with no rules, no boundaries.
与此同时规则和界限都破灭了
They are like an eagle soaring in the sky.
像老鹰一般翱翔于天空
Their lives are in their own hands and they are both aware of it.
他们清楚地知道 命运把握在他们手里
As the point of no return creeps over closer
在两者蠕动地逼近着而且不可能返回的时候
they revisit their past.
他们似乎回到了过去
They recall the hours of training
回忆起过去数小时的训练
every mistake that they ever made and every lesson that they ever learned.
甚至每个犯过的错误和每个吸取的教训
They return ready and there will only be one winner.
当他们回过神来就只有一个赢者了